it's a premium on youth isn't there in
our culture in this business it's
magnified and I learned this when I was
in my early forties helped you just have
to look young for this business and I
was in LA I had a good set so did all
the other young comics early 30s 20s
they have good sets after the show
there's a man in a suit very important
looking across the crowd he was eyeing
all the comics and we thought oh this is
he's a manager he's an agent he's coming
towards us somebody's gonna get a break
who will it be the older guy who's paid
his dues one of the youngsters he came
straight to me only I got his card was
the manager was an agent no he was a
plastic surgeon
oh and I got his last card by the way
plastic surgeon with one card 300 people
I got the card what does that say and I
asked him you think I need surgery I
don't say I mean I've been thinking
about it but do you think I need to sir
I'm not ugly he said we'll come by my
office sometime we can talk about it and
I said well can't you just eyeball a
diagnosis fact did you not just eyeball
it when you gave me your last card
making me the winner of your little ugly
contest can can't they just eyeball it
does anybody know or are these plastic
surgeons like all the other doctors you
know they take your pulse and they weigh
and measure your height then there's
blood samples urine samples stool
samples the plastic surgeons do that
call you a few weeks later with the
results from the lab well we got your
results back sir and you do not look
good much worse than we thought we we
found ugly in your blood
your urine and your stool high levels in
your stool you are but ugly
[Applause]
[Music]
I think you should do something about
this immediately this is you don't want
to die like this
I recommend emergency elective surgery
first thing Monday morning I'm gonna
cancel all the other appointments
they'll be kind of upset because they're
a little ugly too but I'm gonna show me
a picture they'll understand
[Applause]
and then you would say well this is
weird I did not even feel ugly and he
would say well you've probably been ugly
for years just got used to it as did
everyone around you
hey did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch save and share clips and watch my
whole special